teamextension.com 2018-10-01

# Privacy Policy

TeamEXtension respects your privacy in using this site. The following information discusses the practices and the ways your information is collected and used that applies to all pages of this website.

## The Information This Site May Collect

Generally, you can visit and explore this site without revealing any personal information. However, this site has pages that may require personal information from its visitors such as the following:

  1. Name
  2. Mailing address
  3. E-mail address
  4. Phone numbers
  5. IP address

The above details will be kept secured at all times according to the established standards of confidentiality. Any collected information from any of the interactive pages within this site such as the Contact Us page and comment fields and others will not be shared and/or sold to any third parties.

## How Your Information is Used

  1. Contact details that include name, mailing address, phone numbers will be ONLY used to answer your query and to contact you with regard to matters relating to TeamEXtension.
  2. Survey information such as demographic details will be used solely for assessment to improve our system and website.

Our staff are trained and committed to comply with these policies. We continuously improve our system to further protect your information.

## Removing Your Personal Information

If you want TeamEXtension to remove any or all of your personal information from our system or if you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please get in touch with us via our contact form.

TeamEXtension reserves the right to change, modify, or update this Privacy Policy at any time without any notice.

Bookmark/Search this post with
